Is OK a little secret here for your exam success.
No your curves were still pretty early and of course we've covered a lot of material.
There's already been a lot of terms.
Maybe there's some new terms here you've not recognized and maybe some terms you'd need a little refresher
on but from this point forward we're going to really start getting into the Pinback chapters.
It's going to be a lot of terms coming at you.
So what we've done before this has been pretty found found creative foundation pretty fundamental.
Maybe some of this was review for you.
But now we're going to start moving deeper and deeper into the Pinback guy.
There's going to be a lot of terms you need to know for your exam.
So I encourage you to use those flash cards that we talked about is of course resource but also take
notes take effective notes in terms you don't recognize.
Go do a google search look them up look in the Pinback guide.
So if you have downloaded the Pinback guide as being part of a member you get that as part of your membership.
Then you can search for that turn in the Pinback but remember not every term that you're tested on is
in the Pinback guy.
So the Pinback guide is definitely the base but it's broader than just that one document and most the
terms of all the terms they give you are going to be defined in this course.
But if you need more information about the terms that's what Google is for.
So or you can also post the question in the Q&A or look what other people have asked for and so you
really want to make an effort to know your terms the document your terms.
The reason why if you know the terms you'll be able to understand the question better it will be unfortunate
if you get a question you have no idea what you're talking about.
Should that happen to you.
That's probably is one of two things frankly.
One you didn't know your terms.
A term you've never seen before and you were diligent in this course and you really study it might be
a seeded question.
So it doesn't matter.
Another thing to look at though if you get a question and you see there are four choices into those
choices you've never recognized You've no idea.
It might be a bogus couple of the choices those could be some red herrings and distraction for you where
you're not paying attention to the two terms that you do recognize.
Well let's think about this smartly though let's say that the questions asking about risk and you know
the first two choices are risk terms but those terms don't fit with the scenario.
So here are two other choices that you've never seen before you understand these two terms but these
two answers you have no idea.
Well you know these two don't fit.
So it has to be one of these two that you've never seen before.
So now you have a 50/50 shot.
So just by knowing your terms you're doing some critical thinking you're doing some problem solving
that should you get up against in terms you don't recognize you can compare and contrast and from that
make the best choice.
Overwhelmingly though the terms from this course are going to be what you're tested on.
So no your terms.
All right.
Keep moving forward.
You're doing great.